# Allwin raj

# Graphic & Web Designer

A Fresher undergone 1+ Years of Experience On Graphic & Web designing. Allwin is an enthusiastic Learner and Perfervid to designing creative Websites. Allwin can Convert graphic designs to usable web Pages Using Html Css Coding. Planned Website Developments Converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, CSS Coding. He is someone who is fundamentally committed to good practice and innovation and who is very much team player. Always engaged in continuous learning in order to broaden his knowledge and experience

Allwin is currently looking for a Challenging Position to work with a Progressive Company.

# **Recent Project**

https://bit.ly/3MqaOGr

https://bit.ly/3ZTip3x.com

https://bit.ly/3N1Robj

# **My Portfolio Website**

https://allwinathisayam.github.io//cv.github.io/

## **Technical known**

**Figma** 

**CMS** 

**Basics of Github** 

Digital marketing

**Social Media Marketing** 

## **Contact**

#### **Address**

Vallioor, TN, 627117

#### **Phone**

812-405-7406

#### E-mail

allwinathisayam@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/ allwin-athisayam /

### **Skills**

HTML

Excellent

CSS

Excellent

Photoshop

• • • • • • Excellent

Bootstrap

Average

## **Work History**

## **Creative Head - Graphic & Web design**

**2023-05 -** ConnectCorp.in, Trivandrum, KL

**2023-07** This is a Branding based company and all types Gifting solutions. My responsibility in this concern is

doing Graphic Designs and Mockups and Office

Management

2022-07 - Web Designer

**2023-04** WhiteSolutions.in, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu

I have started working as a Entry level

## **Education**

| Bachelor of Engineering : CSE |
|-------------------------------|
|-------------------------------|

**2018-06** Anna University (PET Engg College) Tamilnadu **CGPA** 

(7.79)

2018-04 - HSC (58.5%)

**2017-06** TamilNadu State Board – Tamilnadu, India

2016-04 - SSLC (79%)

**2015-06** TamilNadu State Board – Tamilnadu, India